newcluster.com 2015-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Tech News Cluster

### Visitor Notice

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (Personal Information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you are asked to register and become a Newcluster member in order to participate on the forums, enter into a contest, or opt-in our email newsletters. We use your Personal Information for four primary purposes:

  * To make the site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.
  * To help you quickly find services or information on Newcluster.
  * To help us create content most relevant to you.
  * To alert you about updated information and other new services on Newcluster.

### Visitor Consent

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of the features on Newcluster, but you will not be able to access areas that require registration. Newcluster sends regular newsletters, which are sent only to opt-in lists. They also include a very easy and simple way to be removed once you have joined.

### Security

Newcluster strictly protects the security of your personal information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.

### Distribution of personal information

Newcluster does not distribute personal information to any third parties. Should this change, Newcluster will not distribute any information without your prior express consent. Please be aware that it may be possible, depending on your use of various features on Newcluster, that some of your personal information is available on publicly accessible web pages. One example would be using the Newcluster Forums. Consent to expose some of your personal information in these cases is implied by the use of these features.

### Third Party Ad Servers

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit Newcluster . These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to our site and to other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies may employ cookies and clear GIFs to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and clear GIFs is generally not personally identifiable (unless, for example, you provide personally identifiable information to them through an ad or e-mail message). We encourage you to read these businesses’ privacy policies if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your personal information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, see the [Network Advertising Initiative’s consumer web site](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).

### Hosted Sites

Newcluster gives children between the ages of 13 and 18 the ability to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent. Please take proper measures if you do not wish your child to have access to public forums and message boards. As always, exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in a public forum. In order to comply with the COPPA ruling, if you are younger than 13 years of age, you are forbidden from becoming a member of Newcluster or posting information on Newcluster message boards without direct parental consent.

### Enforcement

If for some reason you believe Newcluster has not adhered to these principles, please [notify us by e-mail](mailto:webmaster@Newcluster.com), and we will do our best to determine and correct the problem promptly. Be certain the words Privacy Policy are in the Subject line.

### Changes to this document

Changes to this document may be made any time without warning. Newcluster may or may not notify you of changes in this policy, however, we will make an effort to notify you if there are any major changes to this policy. You will not be notified about changes related to clarification and/or elaboration of parts of this policy.
